Guide to the John Turrill Carr Lowe notes, 1909-1913.
Lowe, John Turrill Carr notes, 1909-1913
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
John Turrill Carr Lowe notes, 1909-1913.
37-5-595
John Turrill Carr Lowe, 1890-1963.
1.2 cubic ft.
Notes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Lecture notes on courses in economics, education (taught by Professors Bristol, De Garmo, Kimball, and President Schurman), German (Professor Faust), history (Cotterall, Sill, Bretz, and Schmidt), historical geography (Burr), political science (Lagerquist, Bauer), meteorology (Wilson), philosophy (Albee), psychology (Bentley and Ruckmick) and sociology (Willcox).
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Cornell University Class of 1913.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Lecture notes on courses in economics, education (taught by Professors Bristol, De Garmo, Kimball, and President Schurman), German (Professor Faust), history (Cotterall, Sill, Bretz, and Schmidt), historical geography (Burr), political science (Lagerquist, Bauer), meteorology (Wilson), philosophy (Albee), psychology (Bentley and Ruckmick) and sociology (Willcox).
SUBJECTS
Names:
Lowe, John Turrill Carr, 1890-1963.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University. Class of 1913.
Form and Genre Terms:
Notes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- English History. Prof. Catterall. (Box 1)
- Meteorology. Prof. Wilford Wilson., 1911 (Box 1)
- In one volume: (Box 1)
  - Sociology. Prof. Willcox., 1911
  - History & Political Science., 1911-1912
- Miscellaneous Lectures., 1911 (Box 1)
- History 9a (Asiatic History). Prof. Schmidt., 1911-1912 (Box 1)
- Sociology 55. Prof. Willcox., 1911-1912 (Box 2)
- France Under Napoleon. Prof. Catterall. (Box 2)
- In one volume: (Box 2)
  - History 32. Prof. Hull & Bretz., Sept. 1910-Jan. 1911
  - Economic History of the United States, 1787-1910. Prof. Hull., Spring 1911
- Economics 51., Oct. 24, 1910-Mar. 7, 1911 (Box 2)
- Historical Geography. Prof. Burr., 1912-1913 (Box 3)
- History & Political Science 58. Mr. Lagerquist., 1911-1912 (Box 3)
- Psychology 2. Mr. Bentley & Ruckmich., 1911-1912 (Box 3)
- German 30. Prof. Faust., 1911-1912 (Box 3)
- History I. Prof. Sill., First Term, 1909-1910 (Box 3)
- Education 2a (Industrial Education). Prof. Bristol, De Garmo & Kimball; Pres. Schurman., 1912 (Box 3)
- History & Political Science 73 (Principles of Insurance). Mr. Bauer., 1912 (Box 3)
- History & Political Science 68 (Railroad Transportation). Mr. Bauer., 1912 (Box 3)
- Bibliography II. (Box 3)
- History & Political Science 71 (Investments). Mr. Lagerquist., 1912 (Box 3)
- Philosophy 8 (Influence of Philosophy upon Literature in the 19th Century). Prof. Albee., 1912 (Box 3)